welcome everyone in this video we are
欢迎大家在这个视频中我们
going to show you how to connect your
将向您展示如何连接您的
java applications to autonomous
Java应用程序自治
transaction processing using WebLogic
使用WebLogic进行事务处理
server my name is Naimah Lysander Appa I
服务器我的名字叫Naimah Lysander Appa I
am the principal product manager for
是的主要产品经理
Oracle JDBC and UCP let's begin with
让我们从Oracle JDBC和UCP开始
prerequisites the first prerequisite is
先决条件第一个先决条件是
to create an ATP if you have already
如果您已经创建了一个ATP
created an ATP then we are set otherwise
创建了一个ATP，然后设置为其他
sign in with your cloud credentials at
使用您的云凭据登录
cloud.oracle.com and create ATP the
cloud.oracle.com并创建ATP
second prerequisite is to download the
第二个前提条件是下载
client credentials zip file ADP mandates
客户端凭据zip文件ADP要求
a secure connection so Java applications
安全的连接，因此Java应用程序
require either Oracle wallets or Java
需要Oracle钱包或Java
key store files to connect to ATP the
密钥存储文件以连接到ATP
client credential zip file contains all
客户端凭证zip文件包含所有
the required files for the connection
连接所需的文件
now let's see WebLogic server setup
现在让我们看一下WebLogic服务器设置
if you already have WebLogic server then
如果您已经拥有WebLogic服务器，则
we are good otherwise download and
我们很好，否则下载并
install the WebLogic server version
安装WebLogic服务器版本
12.2.2 make sure you point your web
12.2.2确保指向您的网站
logic server to the latest jdk WebLogic
逻辑服务器到最新的jdk WebLogic
server version 12.2.2
服务器版本12.2.2
12.2 JDBC driver but we want you to use
12.2 JDBC驱动程序，但我们希望您使用
the latest 18.3 JDBC driver because it
最新的18.3 JDBC驱动程序，因为它
simplifies the connections to ATP so
简化了与ATP的连接，因此
replace the 12 tor to JDBC driver with
用12替换JDBC驱动程序
the 18.3 JDBC driver in this video we
本视频中的18.3 JDBC驱动程序
will see how to create a data source in
将了解如何在中创建数据源
WebLogic server and this data source
WebLogic服务器和此数据源
will be pointing to ATP and we will also
将指向ATP，我们还将
see how to create a servlet that uses
了解如何创建一个使用
the data source that we have created and
我们创建的数据源以及
we will run the servlet on WebLogic
我们将在WebLogic上运行servlet
server we have the sample that we have
服务器，我们有样本
used in this video on github there are
在github上的这段视频中使用过
two ways to connect to ADP one using
连接到ADP的两种方法
Java key stores and a second using
Java密钥存储和第二次使用
Oracle wallets we will see both these
甲骨文钱包，我们将看到这两个
approaches in this video let's begin
该视频中的方法让我们开始
with creating a data source in web large
在大型网站中创建数据源
server before we do that we have to
服务器之前，我们必须
start the WebLogic server I have created
启动我创建的WebLogic服务器
a project test app in Eclipse and I have
我在Eclipse中有一个项目测试应用程序
added WebLogic server as a server to
将WebLogic服务器作为服务器添加到
this project so let me start the server
这个项目，所以让我启动服务器
you can see that the WebLogic server is
您可以看到WebLogic服务器是
started log into your web logic server
开始登录到您的Web逻辑服务器
console with the username and password
使用用户名和密码的控制台
that you have now we are going to create
您现在拥有的我们将要创建
a data source that connects to ATP for
连接到ATP的数据源
this you need to go to services click on
这你需要去服务点击
data sources and click on new and choose
数据源，然后单击“新建”并选择
UCP data source let's call this data
UCP数据源称为数据
source as a PP data source
源作为PP数据源
let's give jndi name as ORCL ATP
让我们给jndi命名为ORCL ATP
underscore dias
强调dias
we don't want XA let's choose thin
我们不希望XA让我们选择薄
connections copy the database URL and
连接复制数据库URL，然后
Here I am using JDBC test underscore
在这里我正在使用JDBC测试下划线
medium as the TNS alias you can pass DNS
媒介作为TNS别名，您可以通过DNS
admin as part of the database URL make
admin作为数据库URL的一部分
sure you provide the location where you
确保您提供您所在的位置
have unzipped the client credentials zip
已解压缩客户端凭据zip
file this location is important because
归档此位置很重要，因为
client credential zip file contains or
客户端凭据zip文件包含或
JDBC dot properties file this file is
JDBC点属性文件，该文件是
used to specify connection properties
用于指定连接属性
required for either Oracle wallets or
Oracle钱包或
Java key stores enter the database
Java密钥库进入数据库
username password
用户名密码
let's click on next and let's test the
让我们单击下一步，然后测试
configuration we are now successfully
配置我们现在成功
able to connect an ATP let's save this
能够连接ATP，让我们保存一下
data source now we have ATP data source
数据源现在我们有了ATP数据源
that we can use in our servlet the next
我们可以在servlet中使用下一个
step is to use the data source that we
步骤是使用我们
have created in the servlet for this I
已经为此在servlet中创建了
have created a test app project that has
创建了一个测试应用程序项目，该项目具有
UCP servlet in this servlet we will do a
UCP servlet在此servlet中，我们将
jndi lookup to get the data source and
jndi查找以获取数据源和
once we have the data source we are
一旦有了数据源，我们就是
going to get a connection after we get
我们得到之后将获得连接
the connection we are going to create a
我们将要创建的连接
table and insert few records update a
表并插入几条记录更新一个
record and clean up the table so let's
记录并清理桌子，让我们
see how we are getting the data source
看看我们如何获取数据源
you can see that we are using our CL ATP
您可以看到我们正在使用我们的CL ATP
underscore DEA's for the jndi lookup
强调DEA用于jndi查找
before we run the servlet I wanna show
在运行我要显示的servlet之前
you how we are using Oracle wallets our
您如何使用Oracle钱包
jks behind the scenes for this you will
为此，你会在幕后
need to go to the location where you
需要去你的位置
have placed the client credentials zip
已放置客户端凭据zip
file this is the location where I have
文件，这是我的位置
placed the client credentialed zip file
放置了客户端凭证的zip文件
once the important files in this zip
一旦此zip中的重要文件
file is already busy dot properties file
文件已经很忙点属性文件
this properties file contains connection
该属性文件包含连接
properties for both GTS and Oracle
GTS和Oracle的属性
wallets make sure you uncomment the one
钱包确保您取消评论
that you want to use for example for
您想要用于例如
Oracle wallets you need to have the
您需要的Oracle钱包
Oracle wallets related property running
Oracle钱包相关属性运行
the UCP servlet let's go to the test app
UCP Servlet让我们转到测试应用程序
project and click on run as run on
项目，然后单击“运行为”
server we need to invoke UCP servlet
服务器，我们需要调用UCP servlet
you can see that we successfully got a
您可以看到我们成功获得了
connection to ATP for using jks open
使用jks打开到ATP的连接
your ODBC table properties file and make
您的ODBC表属性文件并
sure you comment the wallet related
确保您评论与钱包有关
property and uncomment jks related
属性和取消注释相关
properties this time we are using jks to
这次我们使用jks的属性
connect to ATP make sure you restart the
连接到ATP，请确保重新启动
WebLogic server before you run the
在运行WebLogic服务器之前
servlet
小服务程序
we'll go to test app project and run on
我们将测试应用程序项目并继续运行
server and will invoke UCP servlet you
服务器，并会调用UCP servlet
can see that we successfully connected
可以看到我们成功连接
to ATP using jks thank you for watching
使用jks进入ATP感谢您的观看
the video
该视频